STANDARD FOR LIFE
Wise Man Christopher moves throughout the congregation,
ministering prayer in the name of Jesus Christ.
As he does so, the foundations of the problems in the lives of the people begin to crumble.
All power in Heaven and on earth has been invested in that name Jesus Christ.
At the mention of the name Jesus Christ every force of the adversary has to bow.
As Wise Man Christopher moves along one of the rows, he encounters this man,
and the evil spirit is exposed and begins to verbalise its destructive plans.
Let's watch what happens next.
Fire, in the name of Jesus Christ!
Speak out - who are you!
Why do you want to know?
Jesus wants. Talk!
In the name of Jesus.
Who are you?
I told you that we want to destroy his life.
How many of you? You said "we". How many of you?
We are many.
Mention your names.
I am the wife.
One.
Idol from his family, his father's side.
Two.
Who else?
We have been sent to destroy his life. He wants to serve God.
We are agents of lucifer.
You are agents of who?
Lucifer. We want to kill him. Why does he want to serve God?
In his family, he is the only one. He wants to serve God. Why?
We want to destroy his life.
How do you want to go about it?
We want to kill him.
What means have you chosen to destroy him?
What are the methods?
We wanted to kill him by accident.
When he was coming here, he was involved in two accidents but he didn’t die.
He would be praying every day. Why?
What stopped you from killing him through accident?
He has been praying. He always has the Anointing Water with him. Why?
He always has what?
That water.
How does prayer affect you?
You said he has been praying with Anointing Water. How does prayer...
Don’t you know that it is fire?
It destroys our kingdom.
Look at this.
I don’t want to look at this thing.
Why?
Why do you want me to look at it?
What is in it that is against you?
We don't like it.
It is fire.
That is fire.
Is it the same anointing water that stopped you from killing him?
Yes.
It is the same thing, the same one.
You say that you are an agent of lucifer.
Yes.
Where do you operate from?
We have got so many strategies that we use on him.
We sleep with him in his dreams.
When he wakes up, he would realise that we had come.
He always wakes up in the night waiting for us to come so that he can pray but we never appear to him.
He thinks that he is smart.
We are smarter than him.
Sometimes he doesn’t sleep, he would just be awake to see if we would come.
If he passed out for five minutes, we would come and sleep with him.
We don’t want him to serve God.
When he was coming here, we did everything possible to send him to jail.
He spent two weeks in jail. He was detained at immigration.
Two weeks; he was in jail in South Africa. He was detained.
We did it.
We don't want him to get delivered.
When we sleep with him, he cannot do anything.
When he wakes up, he cannot pray.
Sometimes he cannot even serve in the church he is committed to.
When it is a time to go to church, he would just feel a severe headache we put in him.
Then he would be struggling.
His career - he has been working, doing everything but he will not make it in life.
He has a heart to help people.
We wanted to prevent him from coming here.
First - when he made up his mind to come here - his passport, he couldn't find it.
Who hid the passport?
We did.
How?
We could see what he was planning to do.
So, we hid the passport.
Then he managed - he was praying and fasting - he got the passport.
He was arranging his documents.
We stopped the document at Home Affairs in South Africa.
He wanted to come here and get delivered. For what?
Finally, he managed to do an emergency travel document.
When he got to the airport, he was stopped by a guy there.
They took him to jail. He was crying.
We wanted to kill him.
Is that why he spent two weeks in the prison?
Yes.
Who did it?
We did it.
OK, what is in The Synagogue Church Of All Nations that is attacking both your master - lucifer, and you people?
You are asking me as if you don't know.
Can't you see fire everywhere here? Can't you see that I am feeling hot? Can't you see that?
You people are delivering people, up and down. Why?
What is wrong in delivering people?
Why do you deliver them? They belong to us.
So, you people have been sending them? Those demons?
Those people belong to... We want them to serve us. They should work for us.
What is your work?
We want to kill them. We want to destroy them. It is our happiness.
We sent him this Facebook request.
He refused it and he printed the photo.
He printed the photo, he wanted to show it to the prophet.
We invited him on Facebook with this one.
These are our agents. We wanted him to accept the request.
Then he would die.
What is this all about?
That is our sign. Can't you see?
Your what?
That is your what?
Our sign.
That is one of the signs of our kingdom.
Which kingdom?
Darkness. Lucifer.
What is this all about?
That is the triple six.
What does it mean, and how do you use this figure?
When we send those pictures and you accept it, you become a member of our kingdom.
We would start communicating with you.
Then, we get hold of you and when we do, you can also become a member.
You will serve us. You will also go and get people for our kingdom.
So, whoever sees this thing, that person is in trouble.
What kind of trouble?
If that person is not careful, we get hold of his soul.
Then, that is it for him, he will work for our kingdom.
What "caliber" of people have you initiated?
We especially focus on the youth.
Youth?
Yes, young men and women.
Why do you choose to focus...
They like Facebook.
They like what?
Facebook. They like Facebook, so we invite them.
There are different ways. We get hold of them through that.
A lot of them, they register on Facebook.
They have their photos there.
We go through them and those that are the called ones, we attack them.
How do you attack them?
Sometimes we place our ladies to invite them; they become friends with them.
You place your ladies?
Yes.
What kind of ladies? How? Explain!
They are beautiful.
Beautiful ones?
We have beautiful ladies in our kingdom and very handsome guys.
We send them out there to attack people.
Yes. If you become friends with them on Facebook, you are in trouble.
They communicate with you. Even this guy, he doesn't know; he's confused.
We got his number and he doesn't know where we got his number from.
We called him at night, threatened him, told him he would die and not see 2013
because he made up his mind he would only serve God.
He wanted to come to The SCOAN. We called his number.
How did you get his number?
Through one of our girls.
OK.
Yes.
When you capture this youth that always have their pictures on Facebook, they want to go to the internet,
what will happen to their career, to their destiny, to their future?
They are destroyed. Nothing will work for them. Can't you see this guy?
Before he came here, he sold all his stuff.
They didn't even pay him the money.
A lot of people had promised to assist him before he came here.
He had to sell all his stuff, his laptop, his iPad, everything.
His car, he sold even the car - they didn't pay him.
He struggled. When he got to the airport, he got arrested.
He was taken to court. He paid a lot of money.
He booked a ticket for Saturday, he arrived there - they told him that his ticket had been sold again.
Yes, this is what we do.
Look at these products.
They are all the same thing; it's just that we show up in different ways.
We wanted to frustrate this guy…
Look at the pictures. Whose pictures are these and from where?
That is the sign. That is lucifer.
Please, allow me to go.
You have explained what you did to this man.
I'm talking about the youth. You have succeeded in getting to them on Facebook through these means.
Yes.
What is happening to their career?
Their career is damaged. They will struggle; they will work.
Even at school, they will not perform. When they finish, there is no job waiting for them.
They will be struggling. When they struggle, we are very happy. That is how we enjoy.
Yes.
What will happen to their marriage, if at all they want to get married? What will happen to it?
They will not get married. Through these things - as I said, to some of them we assign ladies.
When they sleep, they are finished. This guy is not married.
When they do what?
When they sleep with them.
What will happen to them?
Then that is it; that is the end. They will not get married unless they are delivered.
That is why we don’t want you to be delivering people here.
That is why you don't want...
Yes. We don't want you guys to be delivering them.
Why?
When you deliver them, their life will change. They will start doing well.
This guy is supposed to be a millionaire.
He was supposed to have a congregation and serve God. We stopped everything.
Sometimes we appear to him as a snake.
We have so many ways we operate.
OK. What will happen to the spiritual life of those youths, that have this?
Those that are the called ones are our targets. They will not serve God anymore.
They will be just sleeping around, committing fornication and adultery.
They will be drinking and smoking. That will be their life and that is our joy.
That is your what?
Our joy.
Your joy?
Yes.
Why?
That is it. That is what we like. Yes.
How many people all around the world have you managed to put into your kingdom through this method?
Millions. You can never imagine. They are many.
How many demonic powers do you possess in this body?
So many powers.
Your end has come.
No.
I don't want to go!
This guy belongs to me.
Didn't I tell you that he belongs to me?
He can't serve God!
Since he was born, we have been threatening his life up to now.
Do you see this scar?
He was sick. They took him to a witch doctor.
Once they cut it, we put a spirit inside.
And you today want to deliver him. For what?
When Jesus says "Yes", no one can say "No".
Out!
Come here!
Fire!
Out!
Come out of this body, you principalities.
Out, in the name of Jesus Christ!
Fire all over your body!
In the mighty name of Jesus Christ!
Out, you demon!
Out!
In Jesus' name. Amen.
Set Free In Jesus' Name
How are you now?
I'm fine, thank you.
You just stood up from the floor.
Yes. I don't know what happened.
You said you were an agent of lucifer.
No. I can't be an agent. I am a servant of God.
You are who?
I am a servant of God, I can't be an agent for lucifer.
No, I can't do that. I love God, I love Jesus.
And you said that you destroyed yourself, you made yourself to sell your properties.
I love myself.
What has happened to your properties?
I sold my properties to get money to come here.
I wanted to come and get delivered, but I never had money.
I have been working but nothing works for me, so I had to sell my things.
And I was not even paid for some of the things that I sold.
We saw that you brought out something from your pocket.
You had something in your pocket before, and you brought it out.
Check, whether you can see it around. What is this?
These are requests that I received on Facebook.
Those are the pictures. I did never accept them.
Bring it, sir. Take it.
Set Free In Jesus' Name
Somebody did what?
Someone sent me these photos on Facebook.
He sent a Facebook request to be my friend.
But I don't know the person.
That person lives close to my house and I thought this person knows me.
I clicked on the photo to check who it was before accepting the Facebook request.
When I clicked it, these photos appeared.
When I saw the photos, I got sick for two days. I stayed in bed. I couldn't wake up.
I used to dream very bad dreams with snakes.
I was hearing voices telling me that I would die.
It became worse since I saw the photo.
Sometimes I could not sleep at night.
Sometimes I see members of my family who died some years ago
I printed these photos so that I could show them to the prophet.
These are the photos.
That demon that destroyed your life, your career and everything about you is out of you.
Thank You, Jesus!
So, you are delivered.
Thank You, Lord!
Thank You, Jesus!
I will serve you forever. Thank You, Jesus!
Set Free In Jesus' Name
Thank You, Jesus!
Emmanuel!
(God with us – Matthew 1:23)
My name is Fabio Adjavon. I'm a citizen of Ghana but I reside in South Africa.
Sir, tell us briefly about your background, about the kind of the family you are from
that enabled this evil spirit to enter you from the very beginning.
I'm from a family of idol worshippers and I grew up experiencing spiritual attacks from time to time,
and nothing I did worked out.
Tell us more about the kind of dreams you were having as you were growing up.
I used to see a snake attacking me in the dream,
sometimes even physically I would walk around and see a snake in front of me,
getting ready to attack me.
I saw dead people in my dreams.
Sometimes I would physically see a very big spider walking on my wall,
which would all of a sudden disappear.
These are some of the dreams and attacks that I experienced.
Growing up I realised that I could see a woman having sex with me.
It disturbed my life. When I woke up, I was very weak and I could not pray any more, I could not do anything.
Tell us more how it affected your career and your zeal to be a Christian, to serve God.
I didn't succeed in anything I did. Spiritually I became "very down".
I could not fulfill my purpose on earth and it disturbed me a lot.
Right now we want to learn from you the area of Facebook,
how this demon actually entered your life through Facebook.
Just tell us more about how that happened.
Were you using Facebook before? What were you using it for? And how did this incident occur?
Yes. I have an account on Facebook.
I usually use it for loading some photos and for leaving messages, the Word of God, and so forth.
When I was arranging my documents to come here, that is when I received this Facebook request
from someone that I do not know.
Tell us more; how did the request come in, and what then happened.
I went to Facebook like any other day to check my messages and other things,
then I realised that someone had sent me a Facebook request.
I didn't know the person.
The request indicated that the person was from the area, where a lot of people from our church live.
I initially thought that person knew me, and it was one of our church members.
You didn't know the person'' name, but you suspected that it was someone you knew very well.
What did you do then?
Exactly.
On the profile picture there were about four people sitting down and drinking.
I clicked on that photo first. That photo was a cartoon, not an image of a real person.
I couldn't see their faces.
I clicked on the photo and started browsing the profile to see who that person was.
That is when I came across these photos.
Tell us - the moment you saw these pictures what happened to you?
It was like something entered me when I clicked on the photo, and I started going through them.
It was like I received something that entered me.
I started to feel very "down", very sick.
You mean to say that the moment you just saw these pictures on your computer,
you felt something physically enter inside of you.
Exactly. I was very shocked. I never expected such a thing.
I felt like something entered me.
So, you mean that you never even accepted the request. You just clicked on the picture to see more,
and that is how something entered inside of you.
Exactly. I never accepted.
I receive so many Facebook requests that I don't accept.
If I don't know the person, I don't accept.
Even if I know the person, I am still very careful.
So, I never accepted that one. I just clicked on the photo to make sure I know the person before accepting.
So, the moment you felt something enter into inside of you - tell us what happened after that.
Then I started to feel very "down", and very sick.
I remember I couldn't do anything for the rest of that day.
I became very sick, I stayed in bed for two days.
What did you begin to see in your dreams after you witnessed these pictures on Facebook?
As I said, I used to receive bad dreams, with snakes and so forth.
After seeing these pictures it became much worse and frequent.
Even in the afternoon - while taking a rest, I would see my family members who died many years ago
coming to me, doing the "normal" stuff - they cook, I eat.
I saw my grandmother telling me that she has come to take me away.
After that, the following night...
Even during the sickness I had to use the Anointing Water
and call some of my friends to come and pray for me.
That is what helped me to wake up the next day.
The following night I received a phone call around 1:40am when I was sleeping.
When I picked up the call, I heard something like a conference - I could hear the person
and other voices in the background as well.
The person was using a microphone to speak, saying that they have been assigned to destroy my life,
so I would not see 2013.
They asked if it wasn't my decision to serve God.
You mean, that physically, after you saw these pictures, you received a phone call?
Was the number hidden, or you saw the number of the call?
It was a "no-number" call.
You said that the first thing you heard was like someone speaking into a microphone and
and there were many people there.
People in the background, like sort of a conference.
What exactly did they tell you on the phone?
This person said that they have been assigned to destroy my life, and that they were agents of lucifer
and they wanted to kill me because I had a calling to serve God, and they didn't want that.
People of God - we can really learn a lot from our brother's experience.
This is a physical thing that happened to him.
He received a phone call from an unknown number after seeing these pictures,
after clicking on the request of Facebook, and physically agents of lucifer called him and said
that they had been assigned to destroy him, and he would not see the year 2013.
Tell us brother, what happened from that point on.
It became very challenging, and at that point I was actually planning to come to The SCOAN.
Things became much worse for me.
I managed to get my document ready.
I had to sell all my stuff to raise that money to come.
During my struggle, sometimes I had a dream, seeing the prophet calling me to come to The SCOAN,
that is where I needed to go to get my deliverance.
After having seen the photos, people promised to assist me financially.
When the time came, no one was picking my calls, or they said they didn't have money to assist me.
So, I had to sell everything.
When I got to the airport...
Before I left, I was involved in two serious accidents.
If not by the grace of God...
I usually have the Anointing Water and the Sticker by my side, any time I'm driving around.
It was just by the grace of God that nothing happened to me.
When I got to the airport, the immigration officer told me that I should stay aside.
I asked, "What did I do?"
Then he told me that I have to spend four years in jail.
I said that he hadn't even checked my document.
Then they went through my document and said that the document was fake, not original.
So they detained me.
Later on they took me to prison.
The first voice I heard in the jail was, "Commit suicide".
I started thinking about that.
I looked around, but there was nothing for me to use to commit suicide.
Another thought that came to my mind was to ask my friend to buy acid, and put it in a coke,
and bring it to me, so I could drink it to die.
The next voice that I heard was telling me to run away from the prison, which I knew was impossible.
The third voice was telling me not to do any of those things.
It became a challenge.
I thought of actually committing suicide, but it was difficult for me to find the means to do it.
In the process I just saw the image of the prophet when he was falsely accused and arrested.
Seeing the prophet encouraged me.
I told myself, "As the prophet became the greatest man on earth after being accused and arrested,
there would be no need for me to commit suicide".
That is how the image of suicide came out of my mind.
You saw the image of Prophet T.B. Joshua in your mind, and recalled how he too was wrongly imprisoned,
and that strengthened you not to commit suicide while you were in prison.
Exactly.
How did you come out of prison and finally made your way to The SCOAN?
I had to call my friends and they had to come and talk to a lawyer.
I was taken to court and they arranged that.
They collected a lot of money and I was released.
They said I could not travel directly to Nigeria, so I had to go to my country first.
I travelled down to Ghana.
I booked my ticket to come here on Saturday.
My luggage was missing at the airport.
I looked for the luggage, but I couldn't find it.
When asked, people at the airport said they did not know where my luggage was.
I had to wait till the following day.
I went back to the airport the following day.
They said that my luggage was still not there.
I was roaming and looking around at the airport and I found the luggage.
When I booked my bus to come here, they said that my ticked was re-booked
and given to another person without any reason.
So, it was a struggle even to come here from Ghana.
We can really understand from our brother how satan was trying every means possible
to stop our brother from coming here.
This is why Prophet T.B. Joshua often says that the greatest mistake satan has made
is allowing you to come here to The SCOAN.
We thank God Almighty that upon all of the odds stacked against him, today our brother is here,
a living testimony that he made it and he is here today to share his testimony.
Sir, tell us - when you finally came what happened when Wise Man Christopher prayed for you.
I thank God for that. I am very excited.
I was touched by Wise Man Christopher, whom I saw few months ago delivering me in The SCOAN.
I even told my friend that it would be Wise Man Christopher that would deliver me in The SCOAN.
You mean you saw it in your dream?
I saw him in my dream a few months ago when I was preparing to come here.
I told all my friends that I had a dream of coming to The SCOAN
and Wise Man Christopher delivered me.
That was exactly what happened when I came here.
When he touched me, I only felt fire.
Even before the wise men came out and started praying for people, when the prophet came,
while he was preaching, it was fire all over my body.
The fire was coming from the ground.
It entered my legs and climbed up my body.
I felt very uncomfortable.
It was surprising to me.
I couldn't believe that while the man of God was preaching, I was feeling fire.
Wise Man Christopher touched me.
I started to feel heat, and that is when the spirit started manifesting.
That is the only thing I can remember, but I thank God for my deliverance.
Wow, let's put our hands together for Jesus Christ!
Tell us, sir, what happened after your deliverance.
After my deliverance I slept very peacefully. I feel very light.
I am very happy now.
I know that the hindrance that stopped me from fulfilling my purpose on earth has been removed from my way.
But there is something that surprised me most.
On Monday I was called to come back here for references, to go through the testimony and so forth.
I had to go back to Facebook.
I wanted to write down the name of the person who invited me, the exact date and time of the request.
To my surprise - the request vanished from my Facebook account.
I couldn't believe it.
Let us put our hands together for Jesus Christ!
Sir, I think you need to explain this, so the people can understand what you are saying.
You mean that the pictures and the request that were given to you vanished after the deliverance?
Yes. Technically that is not possible. I don't know how that happened.
I have a lot of Facebook requests that I have never accepted.
The list of those requests with various dates and pictures is still there.
When I went through that again, I could not find the request from this person, or the photos.
I was very surprised; I had to call my friend to come and witness this.
Even today; there are things that are happening in the spirit.
This is just spiritual, and I thank God for this miracle.
I will never, never, never go back to that life.
Glory be to God.
Sir, how have you been sleeping since your deliverance?
You said before you were always tormented in your dreams. How are you sleeping right now?
I have not received any phone call so far.
I have not had any bad dream. I sleep very peacefully.
Now I have dreams of great things God is preparing for me to do.
I have registered a business.
In the very first week the business was doing well.
After a few weeks people started calling me, saying that they didn't want to be partners anymore.
Those people are now calling me back, asking to be my business partner - I thank God for that.
You mean that after your deliverance you have been receiving phone calls from people
wanting to partner with you?
I was delivered on Sunday. On Monday morning I started receiving phone calls.
Even though I was not in South Africa, people were looking for me through my partners
asking to join my business. I thank God for that.
What can we say but "Thank You, Jesus Christ"!
Sir, right now, I think you are in the position to advise the world, especially the youth,
the young people who are watching Emmanuel TV right now,
and who have listened to this testimony and this experience.
What do you want to tell them about the dangers of the internet and especially Facebook?
My advice to people, especially the youth,
because I know very well that they spend much of their time on Facebook.
They wake up with Facebook and go back to sleep with Facebook,
instead of waking up with prayer and going back to bed with prayer.
They rather wake up with Facebook, and they sleep with Facebook.
I want to tell them, Facebook is not important for your life,
Facebook will not help you to achieve your purpose,
Facebook will not help you to succeed in life,
Facebook will not help you to do well in school, it will rather cause your downfall.
My personal advice to everybody is, Facebook is not important, don't do Facebook.
Unless you only follow the prophet and Emmanuel TV on Facebook, there is no need for you to go there.
Amen. Let's put our hands together for Jesus Christ one more time!
We rejoice with our brother and we thank God Almighty for what He has done in his life
through setting him free from these demonic spirits, and we believe that
youth around the world and people present here have taken their lesson from this experience in life.
We just want to encourage you brother; the best is yet to come.
Continue to make the Word of God the standard for your life, and we believe you will be back here
with more wonderful testimonies in Jesus' name.
Thank you very much.
The prophet said that if anybody wants to open a Facebook account, this person should first of all
go onto his page and pray together with him, before that person can open his own Facebook account.
And those who already have Facebook; if you want to maintain your Facebook account,
the prophet said that you should first of all go on his page and pray with him,
before you go and check your Facebook.
Internet is affecting a lot of people.
I know people that have been destroyed through Facebook.
It all starts with a Facebook request and friendship but with time you realize that you start dating the person,
you start involving in sex and everything, and the devil is destroying a lot of people through that.
I also want to advise those who go to the internet in general.
You might come across a link that will tell you - maybe you are doing a research...
When you click on that link, you will be surprised to see other things, like pornography and so forth.
I am really, really appealing and pleading with the whole world; you have to be very very careful.
Be prayerful when you go on the internet and to Facebook.
There is something that people are doing, which is like a "style" that everybody is doing now:
"online dating" - it is something that the devil is using to destroy people.
You see their adverts everywhere.
Even on posts you see people saying, "If you want to date, if you want to have a boyfriend or girlfriend,
you should go to this website".
I am appealing to you, your life will be destroyed.
Thank you very much.
Fabio Adjavon
Deliverance Testimony